[♪ Theme song]
[Narration] ‘I Am Boxer’
To the winner
Winning prize money of 300 million won
We give you a top-of-the-line flagship SUV.
[♪ Rhythmic music]
[Participant 1 in English] Open the door!
[Participant 2’s elasticity]
[Participant 3 in Korean] Oh my
[♪ Upbeat music]
[Donghoe] So, so much
So familiar, so familiar
[Park Young-ho] It’s been a while, it’s been a while
- [Participant 4] It’s the same, it’s the same
- [Participant 5] Just like that...
[Participant 4] It’s so the same
- [Seongmin] Hello, brother.
- [Hyunjun] Hello.
- [Seungjun and Seongmin] Hello
- [Full-time] Uh
- How are you? handsome
- [Seungjun] Hello
[Seongmin] Are you working hard?
[Park Young-ho] Just work hard
I'm just working hard
- [Ogon] Hello
- [Junseo] Oh, yes
Are you sleeping around here again?
[Ogon] Uh, yeah
I slept near here.
[Park Young-ho] Have you eaten breakfast?
[Standard] I couldn’t eat it.
[Park Young-ho] There’s a lot to eat here, right?
[♪ Bright music]
[Standard] What is delicious?
[Junseo] On this ** side
It was okay to eat it with this sauce.
Well, it smells a bit
It smells like chicken breast.
- [Park Young-ho] Oh, really?
- [Junseo] Yes
- [Standard] Oh, I see?
- Oh, I see?
[Junseo] Protein content
Because it's too high
people who exercise
I think it would be really good to eat
The standard is like this
Do you eat a lot of protein foods?
Yes, but like this
This is my first time with cotton.
[Park Young-ho] Right?
Now
[Junseo] Enjoy your meal
- [Park Young-ho] It’s pasta?
- [Junseo] So
[Park Young-ho] It’s just pasta?
Is it so delicious?
[Standard] Hmm!
No, it's so damn delicious.
[Seungjun] Ah, there aren’t too many people anymore.
Okay, good, good
- There are only strong people, Mr.
- [Standard] Hello
[Full-time]
Only the strong ones remain, now, ha...
[Yoonchan] Please stop fighting.
I'm a pacifist
Let's have a protein drink
[Junseo] Okay, okay
[Park Young-ho] Because there are three flavors
[♪ Upbeat music]
[Junseo] These all taste different.
[Park Young-ho] That’s right, it’s different.
[Junseo’s response]
- [Standard] Is it zero sugar?
- [Park Young-ho] Yes
Can it be sweet like this without sugar?
It feels a bit like that, definitely.
It's delicious
[Junseo] Dieting
It's a really nice world, isn't it?
[Park Young-ho] So, okay
It was a delicious meal
Let's go
[Seongmin] Oh, what are you going to do today?
[Chaehyun] I think you’ll go as a team?
- 5 to 5 to 5?
- [Chaehyun] Uh
How about 3 vs 3 vs 3 vs 3?
[Chaehyun laughs] Uh, 3...
[Yoon Chan] What about 3 vs 3 vs 3 vs 3 vs 3?
[Taekmin] Ah, but
Who will survive today?
There are really 16 people.
What do you think you're going to do, right?
Should I kill him as soon as he comes in?
[Participant’s laughter]
As soon as I came in
Should I kill him as soon as he comes in?
Myeonghyeonman, Myeonghyeonman, Mr.
You don’t think I can kill him?
- [Jongkook] Hello?
- [Dex] Hello
[♪ Rhythmic music]
[Chaehyeon and Yoonchan] Hello?
hello?
[Jongkook] Hey, how?
How is everyone?
- [Full-time] Yes
- [Jongkook] Oh, we’re the director again.
Oh, I've been building up memories for too long
Looking at it
[Sanggeun’s laughter]
Today, Master Ma Dong-seok
Especially for our players
They say they brought a special guest.
[♪ Exciting music]
[Participants’ exclamation]
good
- [Hyunjun] Oh
- I guess a celebrity is coming, right?
[Hyunjun] So
I guess a celebrity is coming
My younger brother does some boxing.
[Participant] Huh? Huh?
oh? Who is it?
[Shin Dong-hyun] ‘A little brother who does boxing’
- [Park Young-ho] Canelo?
- What, what, Mayweather?
[Dex] Amateur record: 283 matches, 268 wins
Professional record: 24 wins in 25 matches
12 KO
Oh?
[Jongkook] Now, WBC
[Hyunjun] WBC?
- W.B.A.
- [Participant 1] WBA?
- IBF, WBO
- [Ogon] Oh
[Participant 2] Huh?
- Isn’t Nao coming?
- [Hyunjun] IBF? A lie
- [Jongkook] Hyeon
- [Shin Dong-hyun] ‘Hyeon’?
Integration of 4 organizations
Light heavyweight champion
[Shin Dong-hyun] Light heavyweight?
[Participants] Huh?
[Chaehyun] Oh, really, who is it?
[Hyunjae] B-Bol, isn’t it B-Bol?
Looks like Deontay Wilder?
Is it really coming?
- Are Beterbiev or Bivol coming?
- [Hyunjun] Huh? Really?
[English] Champion, please come in
[Present is in Korean]
Isn't it B-ball? B-ball?
[Hyunjun] Oh, really?
Wow, wait a minute, Jin, really?
and!
- [Park Young-ho] Wow, I’m crazy.
- [Participants] Wow!
[♪ Magnificent music]
[Dex] I'm a B-ball player!
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Taekmin] Wow, it’s B-ball, B-ball
- [Standard] Wow!
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Taekmin] Wow, it’s B-ball!
- [Donghoe] B-ball, oh, B-ball
[Participants] Wow!
[Taekmin] Wow!
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Participants] Wow!
- [Yunchan] Wow, Mr...
- [Taekmin] Wow
Wow!
[Taekmin] ‘Champion of the four major organizations’
It's like this
'Could it be B-Bol?' I did that
Suddenly a real B-ball came and came
'Oh, before I die
'I'm dying after seeing B-Ball'
Legendary boxer?
Really the best in the world
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Chaehyun] ‘This person is coming?’
I really screamed while doing this.
I was really surprised
Still thinking about it
My heart is pounding, pounding.
A player I respected
It felt like a dream to be in front of me.
It was a little too good
[B-Bol greets in English]
[Taekmin] How did you bring him here?
[Jongkook] Yeah, almost anything
For us boxers, it’s Blackpink.
[Dongseok’s laughter]
[Hyunjun speaks in English]
[Park Young-ho] If this is going to happen, let’s hug
[Park Young-ho’s elasticity]
[Participant] Welcome, welcome, welcome
[Taekmin] Berry, Berry’s big fan
[Taekmin’s elasticity]
Hey, it's just crazy
Wow, I just smelled the belt.
It's crazy now, ah
Big fan, big fan
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Participant 1] Is it true?
- [Participant 2] Wow, that’s cool.
[♪ Intense music]
[Bvol in English] My name is
This is Dmitry Bivol.
He is the unified light heavyweight champion.
[Audience cheers]
[Commentator speaks in English]
Unified champion of WBC and IBF
I'm related to boxing
i love everything
done in korea
When I heard it was a boxing program
I wanted to come right away without hesitation.
Your mother is Korean
That's why I'm connected to Korea
I also want to see the level of Korean boxers.
What ideas do you have with boxing?
I'm also curious about making a program.
who will win
how they do it
I miss you
[Taekmin in Korean]
Wow, so, so...
[Dex] No, our player.
This is my first time seeing you like it this much.
[Taekmin] Wow
[Dex] Than when I won my match
I think I like it
- I really like it.
- [Seongmin] I’m sorry.
Bro, you were on the left side.
[Dex's laughter]
- This is my seat, sorry.
- [Jongkook] You didn’t expect it, right?
[Taekmin] Wow, yeah
It's awesome, wow
It's not CG, is it?
[Taekmin] So
I feel like CG now too
[Dongseok] Now, what now?
In fact, light heavyweights all over the world
[Jongkook] Right
Now we've won everything
There's no one to beat
So there is no one to win
Because I'm taking a break
‘Come in a moment’
[Participants’ response]
So I came
So, clap once, clap
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Taekmin] Wow, big fan, big fan
- [Park Young-ho] Wow
- Does this make sense? Wow.
- [Participant] Thank you, thank you
Wow, when are you going to watch the real B-ball?
Really, this is hard to see in real life.
[B-ball in English]
hello everyone
[♪ Intense music]
Nice to meet you
And in this program
I'm happy to be with you
- [Taekmin] Wow
- [Park Young-ho in Korean] Crazy
[English] Because I came to Korea again
I'm glad
Because it's my mother's hometown.
Because this is my first visit to Korea.
[Korean] Oh, they said it was their first time here
[Bvol in English] To you today
Let me give you some advice.
Even if I can’t give it to everyone
I'll give it to some
- [Taekmin] Hey, hey
- [Park Young-ho] Welcome to Korea
[Taekmin] Hey, hey, hey, I Love You!
[Korean] Wow, I woke up right away.
[Dex] And
Now I want to ask you a question.
Our B-ball player
While boxing
What's most important?
‘What is the Important Boxing’?
Oh, it was very, oh, it was very simple.
- [Dex] Sorry
- [Jongkook] Oh
[Bvol in English] I have all the power
I think it comes from the lower body
[Jongkook’s response]
The lower body acts as an engine.
And the body must act as a wire
Can pack a good punch
[Korean] Oh, is it a bridge?
Something seems different
[Jongkook] Are there any of us players?
To the B-Ball Master
What I really want to ask
If anyone has any questions, yes
[♪ Interesting music]
[Taekmin] Hey, do this carelessly like this
Can I do it? It's almost like I want to
How much boxing do you have to do to get to that level?
Should I ask you something?
How do you eat what you eat?
I want to ask, but
That's a bit much, isn't it?
[Full-time] Hey, weight training
I wonder if you do it separately.
그거 좋은 것 같다, 근력 운동
[English] Yes, of course I do.
There is no need to overdo it
Strength training is a must
I wake up every morning
Run slowly for about 20 minutes.
It's probably about 3km
But once a week
11 km in 1 hour
Mix running with sprinting
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Hyunjun in Korean] Wow, 11km?
[Taekmin] We were doing well.
[Donghoe] So
I was doing well
[Chaehyun] Wow, that’s a lot.
[Taekmin] Just 2 or 3 days with B-Bol
I want to exercise together
[Participant’s laughter]
[Jongkook] Ah, but really, yes
The reason he became the best boxer in the world
There's more
[Dongseok] Sure, sure.
First of all, the world champion b-ball player
This punch
I myself
I'll give it a try, guys.
[Participants’ exclamation]
[♪ Interesting music]
[Chaehyun] I just watched the video of people imitating me
Can you actually see the rhythm?
[Sanggeun laughs] We're moving forward, right?
[Seungjun] Even just a little bit
to look closer
[Park Young-ho] Yes, indeed
You're having all sorts of experiences.
[Hyunjae] Wow, but really
It's definitely different than on the screen.
[Seongmin] I can’t wait to see this picture in front of you
[Taekmin] So
[Dongseok] Jab
Two
one two
[Taekmin] Ah, good
[Ogon and the elasticity of the present]
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Participant 1] It always ends with a hook.
- [Participant 2] So
[♪ Intense music]
[Participant 3] Play with rhythm
[Participant 4] Oh
It's an American gym?
[Dongseok] Two, hook
- Upper, hook
- [Participant 1] Ah, it’s different.
- [Participant 2] Cutting it off is different.
- [Dongseok] Upper, hook
[Participant 3] Huh
[Hyunjun] Wow, he throws it really lightly.
It has impact.
That, that is really scary
[Hyunjun] So
Really impactful
[Taekmin] Because
You have to play all 12 rounds.
You can't hit with force.
[Dongseok in English] Let’s go again
[Hyunjun in Korean]
Until the last check
[Participants] Hey, wow
[Participants’ exclamation and applause]
[B-ball] Thank you
Respect, I Love You!
[Participant 1 laughs]
[Participant 2] Wow
The sense of rhythm is no joke
[Dongseok] It’s no joke
But the punch...
How do you feel? Punch?
Without overthrow
I just play comfortably, comfortably.
All my weight is on me
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Chaehyun] One shot, one shot
Because it hits with power
They tell me to press hard and hit them.
different from us
[Dex] Yes, now for the fourth fight.
Shall we move?
[Jongkook] Yes, yes, it’s good
[Dongseok] Yes, this fight is
B-ball player
I personally prepared it with you.
[Yunchan] Fourth fight
We prepared together?
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Participant] What is it?
[Dongseok] Something I’ve never experienced before
Again?
Another extreme fight
I'm ready
- [Park Young-ho] ‘Extreme’?
- [Taekmin] Please
- [Park Young-ho] Ha...
- [Chaehyun] They’re fighting again
[Dongseok] Yes, the fourth fight
Let's get started right away
[Jongkook] Okay
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Shin Dong-hyun] Oh, what is it?
[Full-time] Ah, what should I do? Ah...
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Narration] Blockbuster
boxing survival
'I Am Boxer' fourth fight
Dear participants
Please enter
[Participant 1] Hey
[Participant 2] What is this?
[Participant 3] Uh, what else...
[Jongkook] Hey, but
This one doesn't have a ring.
I don't know what it will be like
I don't have a ring so I'm going to hit this one.
[Jongkook] So, right? Wow
[Full-time] Ugh...
Oh my
[Seungjun] It’s an arena, an arena?
[Donghoe] A trench, a trench, a trench?
[Present] What the heck
What are we doing today?
Oh, I feel bad
[Dex] Wow, I’m really nervous.
[Bvol in English] Everyone was nervous.
[Jongkook’s response]
‘I Am Boxer’ This fight is
It's a three-way match.
[Participant's elasticity]
[Park Young-ho in Korean]
Wow, three-way battle, wow
Wow
[Junseo] Isn’t it dangerous?
[Yunchan] Is that right, this?
[Chaehyun] How do you fight over there?
[♪ Rhythmic music]
[Narration] The three-way battle
Three players participate simultaneously
Three people fighting?
[Park Young-ho’s Lament]
[Narration] The three players
Take turns with your opponent
Have a one-on-one boxing match
Competition time per round
60 seconds
number of rounds
12 rounds?
[Narration] It’s unlimited
[Participant 1] Wow...
[♪ Exciting music]
Wow, Mr.
[Participant 2] Ah...
[Participant 3 laughs]
[Participant 4] Unlimited
[Participant 5] It’s ruined.
It's too much, really
[Participant 6] Wow, it’s intense.
[Tingling bell sound]
[Narration] The master
Until the end is declared
I'll stop here
[Narration] The confrontation is
It doesn't end
Of the three players who competed together
The survivor
There is only one person
[Participants’ lament]
So there are only five people left?
We're picking five people, then what?
Wow, that's cruel.
[Referee] Stop
[Narration] In case of a KO match
[Referee] Stop!
[♪ Intense music]
[Narration] The KO player survives
The other two players
Everyone is eliminated
[Shin Dong-hyun] Wow, then this is it
never fought
I could be eliminated
[Park Young-ho] Wow, is this supposed to be a KO?
[Hyunjun] We have to KO him quickly.
[Narration] KO victory
If it doesn't come out
Based on master and referee decisions
Survivors are decided
[Seungjun] It’s not easy
[Full-time] Ha, Lord
[Narration] ‘I Am Boxer’
fourth fight
Let the three-way match begin.
[Park Young-ho] There’s nothing to rely on here
There is no ring or cage
It just feels like MMA?
[Dex] Oh, there’s no ring.
Could it be a variable?
Oh, what is this?
Players who are good at this...
- The stadium is small
- [Jongkook] Yes
I have no choice but to fight fiercely
[Dex] Ah
[English] Not good for out boxers
[B-ball] Definitely to Infighter
I think it would be advantageous
[Narration in Korean]
Three-way match, first match
[♪ Suspenseful music]
Back Corner Player
[Dex] Oh, just like this?
[Hyunjun] Who is it? I'm looking forward to it
[Narration] Jo Hyeonjae
[Dex's laughter]
[Dex] Ah, currently
It's out now
[Narration] I will compete with Jo Hyeon-jae.
Hong Corner Player
[Taekmin] Lightweight or mid-lightweight
Do it once and then
Won’t we be the last?
[Seongmin] Just Minwoo Kim
I think I'll go in
[Narration] Kim Min-woo
[Participant's elasticity]
[Kim Min-woo] That, lightweight
boxers
Because I wasn't that alert
‘Oh, it’s really okay for me.’
[Dongseok in English] Minwoo Kim
I'm an MMA fighter
Elite Boxer Vs MMA Fighter
[Narration in Korean]
Cho Hyun-jae and Kim Min-woo will face off against each other.
Cheong Corner Player
Uh, this could be me, but me?
[Chaehyun] Yuk Jun-seo?
[Seongmin] I think so?
[Narration] Yuk Jun-seo
[Park Young-ho] Oh my god
[♪ Heavy music]
Ah...
[Junseo] When the two of you left
I was already preparing, yes
That he is a good player
Because I know
To be honest
I had no peace of mind
I was very nervous
But since we've come this far
Do your best once
Let's see the end
[Jongkook] Back corner Cho Hyeon-jae
engaged in confrontation
Please be prepared.
all the players here
As I sleep less
I know you prepared hard.
From today onwards, no worries
I'll let you rest comfortably
[Participants’ exclamation]
[MC’s laughter]
[Full-time] Provocation, provocation
[Dex laughs] Now the comment is
It's getting fun little by little.
[Jongkook] A little comment
It's like boxing, uh
Among the many mixed martial arts participants
I am the only one left
why is the last one left
Are you a mixed martial arts athlete?
Let’s prove it with today’s game.
[Participants applause]
[Junseo] The only one left
I think he's a non-player
In front of many players
The best fun game
Let me show you.
- thank you
- [Jongkook] Yes
[Songseok’s response]
[English] That’s an interesting combination.
[Jongkook smiles and responds]
[B-ball] A fun match
I think it will work
[Sanggeun in Korean] Wow, three people...
[Laughing] 40 rounds
Aren't you doing it?
[English] Jo Hyeon-jae, right?
[Songseok’s response]
[Dongseok in Korean] Jo Hyeonjae
Outboxing at speed
Because it’s a competitive style
A sense of speed
I think it will be a match
I get tired if I jump that much.
[♪ Pleasant music]
[Jongkook and Dex’s laughter]
[Jongkook] You need to rest, bro.
If you do that much
- If you do that much, you should take a break.
- [Jongkook] You need to rest, bro.
[English] How about Minwoo Kim?
How is he doing in MMA?
- [Dongseok] Good job.
- [B-ball] Oh, are you good?
- I'm good at MMA.
- [B-ball] Are you good at MMA?
[Dongseok] MMA is based on boxing
[♪ Heavy music]
[B-ball] Oh, I see.
[Songseok’s response]
[Jongkook in Korean]
Ah, but Yuk Jun-seo is special, really.
Do you feel anxious the whole time you watch it? uh
A little today
You should be careful, maybe
[Jongkook] Yes, it’s okay today
Because the friends I've had so far
These guys are all completely technical
I didn't have it
[Dongseok] That’s right
Fighting with non-boxers
[Jongkook] But today is now
Because they are people who use their fists a little
[Dex] So you might be very confused.
I think there is, rather
[Jongkook] That’s right, that’s right
I'm talking about stopping you, really.
[Dongseok in English] You
Please say 'box'
- I'll tell you.
- Yes
[Narration in Korean]
Round 1 of a three-way match
[♪ Suspenseful music]
Jo Hyeon-jae and Kim Min-woo
Please come to the center of the ring.
[Hyunjun] Oh, the size difference
Are you feeling better?
[Hyundai] When we actually met face to face
I'm shorter than I thought
'I guess this could be easy to do?'
box
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Box
[Participants] Fighting!
[Jongkook] Hey, I have to do this well.
[Seongmin] Hyeonjae
Take it easy, take it easy
[♪ Nervous music]
Ah, again, again, greed, just tap, tap
[Jongkook] Why is your face like this?
Does it always happen like that?
You have to cover it well, you have to cover it well
[Dongseok] I took a step back and then
Wow, good
- [Participants] Hey
- [Dongseok] It’s dangerous
[Oh Gon] Hyunjae, don’t give me credit.
[Seongmin] For sure
Defense needs to move more
[Seungjun] But it’s bigger than you think
Because the ring is narrow
To MMA people
It could be more advantageous
- [Participant 1] That’s right.
- [Participant 2] Oh, good.
[Taekmin] Oh, Mad Dog is doing well.
[Park Young-ho] Fighting, fighting
[Present] For the first time with Minwoo Kim
When competing
Maybe it's because I'm not just a little arrogant, but also arrogant.
Uh, I think I stopped him a bit in the beginning.
If you think too lightly now
It doesn't work, yeah
Currently the punching power is
Because it might be a little weak
with technique
- [Participant] Hey
- [Soapseok] Fish oil
nice body
Do it from afar, do it from afar
It's long, it's long, it's the present
[Elasticity of the end]
[♪ Exciting music]
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Dongseok] The counter was correct.
Ooh, nice uppercut.
[Chaehyun] Stay calm, stay calm
Make it calm
[Ogon] The round is long, it’s now
Oh, it's good
[Tingling bell sound]
- [Referee] Stop
- [Chaehyun] Hey, it was good.
[Dex] Okay, round 1
Looking at each other
[ding bell sound]
[Dongseok] Is Junseo holding up well here?
What is your physical strength?
[Dex] That’s right
[Junseo] First, watch the match between those two
After watching
It's time to go in
How should I fill the round?
Think about that
I think I was going to try it.
- [Jongkook] Oh, in and out
- [Participant 1] Fighting
[Participant 2] Oh, it’s better, hey
[Participant 3] Oh, nice
It's neater than you think?
Good, good? uh?
[♪ Nervous music]
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Seungjun] But
You've been practicing a lot.
[Dongseok] Yuk Jun-seo
The rhythm got better, the rhythm got better
Because there was no rhythm?
[Dex laughs] Very interesting.
Are you looking at me now?
The steps are better than before
- More than two weeks ago
- [Dongseok] Uh
[Dex laughs] So
It seems like everyone keeps improving, this
[Jongkook in English]
I like Yuk Jun-seo
[Participant 1 and Seokseok’s elasticity]
[Participant 2 in Korean]
Just head, just head
[Dongseok] Rather, a bit of distance
You're adjusting it well, Yuk Jun-seo.
[ding ding bell]
- [Referee] Stop
- [Dongseok] Okay, okay, it was good.
It was good, it was good
[Park Young-ho] It’s hard, do it right away
It's not easy
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Box
[Current] Yuk Jun-seo
What style is it?
I don't quite understand
‘First, I have to hit a lot quickly.’
I thought about this
[Seongmin] That’s right, that’s right
[♪ Nervous music]
Galak malak, galak malak, galak malak
- [Seungjun] But he’s good at it
- [Seongmin] I worked hard.
[Chaehyun] Is your stomach very empty now?
Hey, good
[Seongmin] Greed, greed
Greed, greed, greed, greed
- You have to hit one pear, one pear, one pear.
- [Chaehyun] Jab, jab, jab, jap
[Seungjun] Hyeonjae is gearing up.
[Dongseok] Junseo
Is your head falling too far back?
- It's dangerous, then.
- [Seongmin] Painting a lot
[Jongkook] Too off center, backwards
[Dex] But if you do things like that right now,
I feel like I'm going crazy, this is
I think it will be very difficult
[Park Young-ho] Fighting!
[Seongmin] That’s right
[Dongseok] That timing
It's hard to wake up
Junseo is over there
You won't be able to give it your all, now
- [Dex] That’s right.
- [Park Young-ho] It’s fast, wow
[Seongmin] Don’t lose strength, it’s Hyeonjae
Don't lose your strength
[ding ding bell]
[Park Young-ho] Fighting, good job
[Dongseok] You fought well, you did well.
[Park Young-ho] Oh, breathe, breathe
Junseo, you’re tough.
Breathe, breathe
[Dongseok] From Junseo’s perspective,
It must have been very difficult right now.
What I'm doing with Hyunjae
[Junseo] Definitely better than my movements
I think it was much better
overall
‘Ah, this is where strategy is important.’
I think I had this thought
[Seongmin] Don’t go in too much.
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Box
[♪ Intense music]
- [Taekmin] Hey
- [Seongmin] Hey, right
If you give it, it will come out.
[Kim Min-woo] I use the boxing rhythm
If you follow
Because you might not be able to catch it
To get closer to the fight
I thought about it and went in.
[Seongmin] Play, play, play, play
Yes, yes, yes
[Dongseok] Good, those movements are good
[Seongmin] Come now
[Oh Gon] Hyunjae, don’t give me credit.
[Dex] Kim Min-woo is strong
This is power
There seems to be a little difference.
[Dongseok] There is a difference
The present is a bit lighter
So you have to cover it properly.
- Yeah, we have to cover it.
- [Seongmin] Ah, I ran it well.
[Currently] I’m sure it’s because he’s an MMA athlete.
As if digging in
I felt it
‘Don’t get excited, stay calm’
‘Let’s show a clear impact’
[Participants’ exclamation]
- Oh wow
- [Dongseok] Oh...
Nice uppercut
[Dongseok] Jo Hyeon-jae
Uppercut timing is an art.
[Chaehyun] Please come in.
[Seongmin] Ah, I like that kind of thing
- [Yoonchan] From far away, from far away
- [Seongmin] Get the rhythm, rhythm
[Ogon] That’s right, enjoy it
Yes, yes, yes
[Chaehyun] Straight
straight, neat
It's straight
[Seongmin] Oh, it’s good
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Seongmin] Oh, it’s good.
- [Dongseok] That’s right, oh my, oh my
[Seongmin] Where are you going, where are you going?
[Park Young-ho’s laughter]
Don't lose your strength, don't lose your strength
Got showmanship, now
[ding-ding-ding bell]
[Referee] Stop
[Chaehyun] Well done, good job
[Park Young-ho] He’s good at it, really.
[Jongkook] Ah, but
Well done Kim Minwoo, you are doing well.
[ding bell sound]
[Dongseok] Now, here
What happens from here now?
[Dex] Here again now
Yook Jun-seo
They're going to try to eat some, right?
Because you will be out of stamina
[♪ Exciting music]
[Jongkook] That’s right
fish oil, fish oil
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Dongseok] No, it’s like that.
That's my specialty
[Dex] Wow, something like that
If you really get it wrong...
[Dongseok] But a little bit
It's good to lose a little bit of strength.
- [Chaehyun] I’m a little scared of this.
- [Referee] Box
[Participant 1] While breathing
- [Participant 2] Hey, hey
- [Participant 3] Wow
[Dex] Oh, yeah
You should use it like this
person with low physical strength
I have to catch it and eat it.
[Participant 4] Hey
[Junseo] ‘Physically,
Even if it's difficult'
'Keep guard up
‘I just have to push forward.’
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Referee] Stop
- [Dex] Style is coming out now
[English] Yuk Jun-seo
The power is really good
[Jongkook] That’s right, that’s right
[B-ball] Innate strength
I think it's good
[Dex in Korean] Clearly KO
I think it's a fist that can come out
Yuk Jun-seo
[Kim Min-woo] I also worked with many players
We train together
I never felt it there either
Because it was a fist of something
[♪ Heavy music]
'It won't be easy'
- [Full-time] Fighting, fighting
- [Park Young-ho] Fighting
- [Dongseok] Sangseong and Yuk Junseo are now
- [Referee] Stop
- Kim Min-woo is winning.
- [Dex] So,
- I think so too.
- Keep going, uh.
I'm beating Minwoo Kim.
[Dex] But for Jo Hyeonjae
I'm a little embarrassed again
[Dongseok] Junseo is very tired
Currently, I have to go now
[ding bell sound]
[Jongkook] Yuk Jun-seo
This time will be difficult, this time
I think this time will be difficult, this time
[Chaehyun] Just put the cover on, right?
That's right
[♪ Heavy music]
[Jongkook] Ah, Jo Hyeonjae
I'm just going in, huh?
Just infight
Coming in, Jo Hyeonjae?
[Dex] Uh, the present is
Originally, I was out fighting.
Oh, but it just goes in completely.
[Dex’s response]
It's not really your style, is that it?
[Currently] I guess this game is
Whoever KOs first
Because I'm winning
When I get a chance
I said I should KO him first.
I thought
[Park Young-ho] I guess I’m greedy
[Yoonchan] Take it easy, Hyunjae hyung, just
[Jongkook] Targeting the body from below
Aiming for body
Targeting the left, left body
[Dex] Ordinary people like us
How many times does that body get hit?
- [Jongkook] Uh, eggplant, eggplant
- [Dex] I'm a little embarrassed, really.
[Park Young-ho] A little bit
It feels like I'm aiming for KO?
[Chaehyun] Distribution of stamina, distribution of stamina
[Participant 1] Definitely defend
[Participant 2] 15 seconds
- [Jongkook] Oh, I went in.
- [Participant 3] Hey
[Dex] That body is dangerous
Hey, hey
[Jongkook] That’s what I’m aiming for, that one
[Taekmin] You have to take it lightly
Waving it
[Dongseok] To see the match this time
I think so?
[Dex] Within one or two rounds
Would you like to see a match?
Hey
[Tingling bell sound]
[Referee] Break
I'm losing my strength
[English] It was good, it was okay
It wasn't Jo Hyeon-jae's style, though.
It was good
[Present is in Korean]
Uh, I tried Infighter too.
I also tried outboxing.
I tried both
Now, I'm definitely used to the other person.
‘I have to show the fear of a boxer’
[♪ Exciting music]
[ding bell sound]
[Seongmin] It’s coming, now? Just, hey!
[Chaehyun] You like left-handed people.
Hey
[Participants’ exclamation]
Oh my
[Seongmin] That’s right
That's right
[Chaehyun] Hey, it’s good
Fake it like this, turning it like this
[Referee] Box
[Seongmin] So in such a hurry
You don't have to
Uh, right, right, right
[Jongkook] You have to go to Bodhi, Bodhi
Let's hit just one hit
- [Seongmin] Hey, right
- [Dex] 5 seconds
[Participant] Hey
[Seongmin] Play more, play more
[Tingling bell sound]
[Park Young-ho] You held on well
[Shin Dong-hyun] Yes
I heard that friend is really good
You're so good
- [Dongseok] Junseo can’t guess right now.
- [Dex] Yes
[Junseo] The current player
Because it doesn't suit me
It's a tricky style.
Comparatively, with Kim Min-woo
It's time to play
It suited my style more.
[♪ Exciting music]
[ding bell sound]
- [Dongseok] Push me away
- [Jongkook] Look at this, push it all away
- You push me away.
- [Participant] Hey
It's just a bull fight.
It’s a wild beast, a wild beast, wow
[Junseo] ‘I’m here
'The way to win'
‘I need to KO Kim Min-woo’
- [Park Young-ho] Come on, fighting, fighting
- [Full-time] Fighting
[Dongseok] I don’t know how this will turn out
now not yet
There may be a download
Ah, if only one person gets KO'd
You two keep fighting?
[Shin Dong-hyun] No, no, no
If I KO you
I live alone
Two people fall
[Participant 1] My child, Junseo
I can send one person
[Participant 2] Hey
[Jongkook] Ah, but Minwoo Kim
If you have some stamina
I have to go in now
Yook Jun-seo is very tired now.
[Dongseok] Yuk Jun-seo is doing really well.
[Dex] Right?
Uh, I'm doing well with the players.
[ding bell sound]
[Dex] And
Jo Hyeon-jae and Kim Min-woo
- The style is different again.
- [Jongkook] That’s right
[Dex] So keep going
Because I fight with other styles
I don't think it will be easy
[Chaehyun] Hyeonjae, lightly, tok tok
[Shin Dong-hyun] Relax, it’s Hyeonjae.
[Full time] Hey
[Junseo] With Jo Hyeonjae
When playing a game
‘You have to endure it no matter what’
I thought about it
Hey
[Dongseok] But it’s still great
Like that now
Trying to somehow break that rhythm
I'm doing it now
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Box
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Dex] Hey, hey
[Participants] Hey
Hey
[Yunchan] Let’s go first, let’s go first
[Junseo] Things like physical arrangement
Actually don't worry
I keep hitting it with as much force as I can.
I need to KO Kim Min-woo.
Now there's no place to retreat anymore
I'm thinking
[Participants’ elasticity]
[Yunchan] I’m going, I’m going
[Park Young-ho] Looks like he’s relaxed
[Chaehyun] I feel better now
[Dongseok] Wow, as expected
[Dex] Hey, like that
Still throwing quick jabs
- [Seongmin] Turn around, hey
- [Park Young-ho] Hey, hey, you’re good.
I avoid it while watching everything.
[Park Young-ho] Wow, it’s tough.
[Dongseok] Everyone is very tired.
[Dex] I'm starting to get tired now.
- [Yoon Chan] It’s tough.
- [Park Young-ho] It’s not over
Is this really a death match?
[ding bell sound]
[♪ Exciting music]
- [Participant 1] Tuktuk
- [Participant 2] Hey
You have to focus until the end, focus until the end
[Seongmin] Don’t be greedy
Don't be greedy, it's coming, it's coming
- [Dongseok] Hyeonjae has great physical strength.
- [Dex] That’s right.
[Dongseok] Keep running around like that
It's very difficult
Wow, he's still running like that.
[Seongmin] That’s right, take your time
[Dongseok in English] Jo Hyeonjae
I have good cardiorespiratory endurance.
You're still running around
I can still move
[Songseok’s response]
Over 20 rounds
I think I can fight
- [Seongmin in Korean] Hit it!
- [Dongseok] Ah, it was good.
- [Participant 1] Hey
- [Seongmin] Don’t be greedy
- [Participant 2] If this happens, I don’t know.
- [Dex] 5 seconds
[Participant 3] Fish oil
[Current spirit]
[Participant 4] Hey
Oh my...
[Tingling bell sound]
[Sanggeun laughs] ‘Ouch’
[Participants’ laughter]
‘Ouch’, ‘Ouch’ at the end
[MC’s laughter]
Ah, this time
Minwoo Kim is in a bit of a crisis right now.
I'm so tired now
I met a recharged Yuk Jun-seo
[Dex's laughter]
[ding bell sound]
[Dex] Look, look
It's charged again, just like that
[Participants] Hey
Hey
[♪ Exciting music]
[Participant] Hey
[Junseo] ‘It’s another chance again’
‘I really have to KO him this time’
- [Chaehyun] Fighting, both of you
- [Seongmin] Fighting
[Jongkook] Hey, rather, Minwoo Kim
Avoid Yuk Jun-seo
Are you going to Jo Hyeon-jae?
[Current] Yuk Jun-seo
Minwoo Kim
It attacked strongly.
'I guess I could be KO'd first?'
I was a little anxious
[Chaehyun] I squeezed in a little and took a shot.
[Participant's elasticity]
[Same seat] 10 seconds
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop!
[Park Young-ho] Good, good
Ah, this time, Yuk Jun-seo
This is the problem now, yogo
Is there a bit of a problem this round?
[Dex’s response]
Uh, this time, now
Jo Hyeonjae is in good spirits right now.
‘Round 21’?
[Hyunjun] Wow, it’s really unlimited.
Fighting!
[ding bell sound]
- [Participants] Fighting!
- [Referee] Box!
[Dex] Neither of us have any regrets
Gotta pour it out, just
- [Participant] Hey
- [Dex] Show me everything, everything!
- Show me everything, everything.
- [Participant] Hey
[Seungjun] Ah, mental strength...
[Dongseok] Oh, it’s good
Those jabs, those
[♪ Intense music]
Oh!
Hey, I got caught.
[Seongmin] Hey, this
Hey, is this a chance?
[Full-time] I have to go
[Hyunjae] ‘I think it’s the last time’
'Just let me KO him'
'I have to finish it'
As expected
[Jongkook] Left hand double
[Participant] Hey
[Jongkook] Oh, that’s right, Bodie
Yeah, I went in, just a little while ago.
[Participant] Guard goes down
Guard goes down
[Jongkook] Only the body has to go in.
That's right
Yeah, I'm in, I'm in
You're in now, you're in now
[Participant] Curly
My stomach was twisted.
10 seconds left, get over it
[Dex] 10 seconds!
[Kim Min-woo] We’re all here
We're all here, we're all here
- [Participant 1] Fighting, fighting!
- [Participant 2] 3 seconds!
[ding-ding-ding bell]
[Referee] Stop
[Tingling bell sound]
[Park Young-ho] It’s over
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Tingling bell sound]
[Park Young-ho] Ah, you had a hard time
[Seungjun] I really did a lot
[Dex] Ah, the last one was dangerous.
I really wish I had 30 more seconds
- Could it have been downloaded?
- You can, uh, right.
[♪ Music full of tension]
[Narration] I will announce the results
[Participant 1] Current price
Wouldn’t he have won?
[Participant 2] Here, I am here
[Junseo] Honestly
I worked really hard too
I was looking forward to it.
Referee decision result
The survivor of this fight is
This is back corner Jo Hyeon-jae, yes.
[Park Young-ho] You worked hard
[Participant] Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work
[Sanggeun sighs] Oh, I’m nervous.
The further back you go, the scarier it gets.
[Chaehyun] Ah, next time...
[Narration] Three-way battle
[♪ Upbeat music]
Let's announce the next contestant
[Full-time] Boy, I am like this
Are there only scary people left? Ah...
[Participant 1 laughs]
[Participant 2] I’m scared, I’m scared
[Participant 3 laughs]
[Participants’ laughter]
[Narration] Back corner players
- Lee Chae-hyun
- [Current] Fighting, fighting
[♪ Interesting music]
[Chaehyun] When I said, ‘It’s a three-way match.’
I was really confident
A bit like the rules of the game
You've been training a lot, right?
Physically, you must go.
Yes, I was confident I would win.
just in the ring
I'll show you with boxing
[Narration] I will compete with Lee Chae-hyun
Hong Corner Player
[Park Young-ho] Please, please
[Narration] Lim Yun-chan
[Participants’ exclamation]
[♪ Upbeat music]
[Same guest] Lim Yun-chan
He's a good straight player.
Richie is 192
Eh?
[Jongkook] Hey, it’s long, long, long
[Narration]
Chae-Hyun Lee and Yun-Chan Lim will compete against each other.
Cheong Corner Player
Shin Dong-hyun
- [Minwoo Kim] Fighting
- [Park Young-ho] Donghyun, fighting
[♪ Heavy music]
[Shin Dong-hyun] I am a Muay Thai athlete.
I had a fight with two boxers.
No less than a boxer
Look like a boxer
let me show you
Because I'm not a boxer
People who are not boxers
I think I'll be rooting for you
[English] Shin Dong-hyeon
I belong to a *peanship.
- Won *peanship?
- [Jongkook] Yes, won *peanship
-You're good at it.
- [Jongkook] Yes, I’m good.
[Dongseok] He is a very aggressive player.
[B-ball] That’s my style
[Songseok’s response]
[Korean] Yes, next
Lim Yun-chan from Hong Corner
engaged in confrontation
Please be prepared.
[Yunchan] Oh, against such strong opponents
It's so nice to be able to stick together
Also, with Chaehyun hyung,
I have some things to pay back.
[♪ Rhythmic music]
Rival?
Chaehyun hyung?
With Yun Chan
I thought I'd like to join you
He is also my favorite younger brother
[Yoon Chan] He’s a close person.
That I can do it
On the one hand it was good
I made an appointment
I've never been able to do it, until now.
And because I'm in the military
[Chaehyun] Huh?
What I know, what I know, Lim Yun-chan
He's back
I didn't even know it was coming out
Nice to meet you here
[♪ Lively music]
Hey, Lim Yun-chan
[Yoonchan] Hengnim
No, why are you wearing a military uniform?
-Anyway...
- [Yunchan] Will you survive?
Oh, I have to survive
Even if I die, I won't fall
‘Investigation failed’
What is it like?
It's starting again
[Yoonchan] We used to spar a lot.
earlier this year
When I was rehabilitating
The first thing I did was
Because Chaehyun was my older brother.
[♪ Bright music]
I think I naturally cheered for him.
Yunchan, you’re doing well.
Let’s go Lim Yun-chan!
[Yoonchan] Actually, Chaehyun hyung
I respect
Cool, Lee Chae-hyun!
Chaehyun hyung, fighting!
But when I close my eyes and open them
There were fifteen people left.
I got a little greedy
I know you're good at it, but
‘It’s worth a try’
Because I thought about it
I was confident
[Yoonchan] A little better this time
I will try my best to show you
[Chaehyun] Let’s have fun
[Yoonchan] Yes, I like it
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Park Young-ho] It feels a bit like 2 to 1?
[Park Young-ho’s laughter]
[Kim Min-woo] A lonely fight
It could be possible
[Park Young-ho] So
It feels like 2 to 1
[Narration] Let the showdown begin
[♪ Rhythmic music]
Box!
[ding bell sound]
[Participants] Fighting!
[Dex] What a fun game
Do you think it will work?
[Jongkook] Hey, because they are both
I can't guess well
[Dongseok] Uh
[Hyunjae] Up to the hook, hyung, up to the hook
[Participant 1] Oh, I took a good picture.
[♪ Nervous music]
[Jongkook] Both are far away
[Elasticity of soapstone]
- [Current] Bbabam
- [Jongkook] Wow
[Present] Uh, jab, jap, jab, jap!
- [Participant 2] Hey
- [Hyunjae] I like the hook, too.
- It's a counter fight, a counter fight.
- [Jongkook] So
[Dex and Jong-guk’s elasticity]
[Dongseok] Oh, I got one count right.
[Chaehyun] Lightly use your front hand
I did it like I was practicing
Just have a good jab
I was confident
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Jongkook] Wow, that’s a lot, uh
Lee Chae-hyeon
They're being pretty aggressive right now, aren't they?
From the beginning
[Participants’ exclamation]
Oh, Lee Chae-hyeon
This is definitely a skill...
[Jongkook] You’re good, you’re good.
[Current] 10 seconds, 10 seconds
Chaehyun Lee, 10 seconds
10 seconds, okay, take it out, take it out, take it out
[Seungjun] I’m really good at avoiding it.
[Participants’ elasticity]
[Tingling bell sound]
[Park Young-ho] It’s fun
[Kim Min-woo] Shin Dong-hyun fighting
[clap clap sound]
[Participant] Fighting
[ding bell sound]
[Participants] Fighting
[Participants’ elasticity]
[Dongseok] Lim Yun-chan
Straight is good
[♪ Exciting music]
[Jongkook] Oh, it’s long, it’s long
[Yoonchan] Oh, but it’s neat, right?
Put it below, connect above, and reconnect!
It's an outstretched fist.
fist stretched out
[Jongkook] It starts a little slowly.
- overall
- [Dex] That’s right.
[Participant] 5 seconds!
[Dex] Okay
This round is a battle of exploration
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop
[Jongkook] We are entering a search war.
[Dongseok] Both of you stay calm
I played it
Now, what happens here?
[ding bell sound]
[Participant 1] Fighting
[Dongseok] Stay here
It feels like they're going to fight each other, right?
[Participant 2] Hey!
[Minwoo Kim] Center
I think you can lower it a bit
[Present] Pressure, pressure, pressure
Okay, press again.
[Seongmin] I really like the front hand
[Minwoo Kim] Blue
I think it's a bit passive.
[♪ Meaningful music]
Shin Dong-hyeon
Or are you feeling a bit unwell?
[Shin Dong-hyun] I planned a strategy
Watching the previous game
It lasted up to 20 rounds.
‘Let the two fight as much as possible’
‘Let’s save our strength until round 10’
Now I continue
I was working on my physical strength.
[Jongkook] Boy, Shin Dong-hyun is a bit real
Useless stamina
I'm trying not to use much.
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop
[Dongseok] Now Shin Donghyun...
[Dex] I’m looking at you
Don’t you feel it?
[Dongseok] Timing report
I think I'm looking for a shot now
Looks like I'm aiming for a shot
[ding bell sound]
[Standard] Oh, it's definitely a front-hand fight...
[Seongmin] Good front hand
[Jongkook] But Lee Chae-hyun
It's a bit long so I can't get it right.
[♪ Exciting music]
[Participants’ exclamation]
Ugh!
[Yoonchan] Look at all the fists
To keep some distance
I tried
Because I have a much longer reach
- [Participant] That’s right!
- [Songseok] Hey! Good, good, good
[Participant 1] Hey
- [Participant 2] Hey, hey!
- [Participant 3] That’s right.
[Park Young-ho] Oh, it’s killing me
Lim Yun-chan is now countering.
I'm guessing well now
[Dex’s response]
[Dex] Straight
It's my specialty, that's it
I think it would be a bit dangerous if I got caught, right?
[Chaehyun] I was really surprised, really.
As the second half progressed, Yun Chan
It came back to life a little bit.
Lee Chae-hyun must not let down his guard either.
- [Participant 1] Hey
- [Participant 2] 5 seconds, 5 seconds!
[Participant 3’s elasticity]
[Tingling bell sound]
[Referee] Stop!
[Participant 1] Hey
[♪ Interesting music]
[Jongkook] I have to go, I have to go, fist
[Jongkook and Dex’s elasticity]
[Participant 2] Hey, hey, hey, hey
[Yoon Chan] To Shin Dong-hyun
step by step
I was trying to change the tempo a little bit.
[Taekmin] By Lim Yunchan
I think he has good distance control.
[♪ Urgent music]
[Minwoo Kim] It’s big, it’s big
When the timing comes
I'm trying to go in with a bang.
It's not going well right now, that's it
[Participant] Good, good, good
[Dongseok] Straight then punch
[ding bell sound]
[Participant] Are you starting to feel it now?
- [Dex] These two are on fire?
- [Referee] Break
[ding bell sound]
[Hyunjun] I have to throw a few.
Throw, like now, okay
Muay Thai fist
[ding bell sound]
[Present] Yes, up to the hook
- Jab, jap, jab, jap, jap.
- [Participant] That’s right, it’s coming, hey!
It was actually kind of easy.
‘Ah, I won this’
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Box!
[Kim Min-woo] Fighting, fighting
[Seungjun] Fighting, fighting!
[Current] Foot, foot, foot, Lee Chae-hyun, foot
[Participants’ exclamation]
[♪ Intense music]
[Participant] Ooh, ooh!
You'll get hurt, be careful
[Dongseok] You can’t get excited.
- [Chaehyun] Are you okay?
- [Yunchan] I just can't help it...
- [Chaehyun] Oh, it's torn?
- [Referee] Stop
- Oh, it's torn?
- [Referee] Stop, stop, stop
[Participant] It stopped
[♪ Heavy music]
[Referee] Stay still
It hurts, it's torn here.
[Jongkook] Ah, Butting is here.
[Chaehyun] Are you okay? Ah...
[Referee] Doctor
Is there cutting?
[Full time] Big, cutting was done
[Referee] Time, doctor
time, doctor
[Taekmin] Oh, I’m bleeding
[Full-time] Oh my, fish oil
You might be a little dazed right now, right now.
[Yoonchan] Chaehyun hyung has a fast tempo
As I tried to match the tempo
Butting occurred.
[Chaehyun] Is Yunchan in a hurry now?
Put the cover on
He said he was trying to infight.
As soon as we hit it
'Oh, this must be torn?'
I looked at him and said,
It was torn
Ah, so 'Ah, I'm sorry'
First of all, I'm sorry.
To Yun Chan
[Chaehyun] I’m sorry, ah...
If you have a scar on your face
claim compensation for damages
[Chaehyun] Oh, I’m sorry.
[Participants] Oh my
[Participant] One? Do you want to do it?
I'll check with the doctor and do it.
Check if the game can be played
[♪ Heavy music]
[Referee] Just stop the bleeding, please.
Yes, just stop the bleeding
blood at first
Did it get in your eye?
[Participant] But this is
Cutting with me, indeed
Do I need to sew this?
What happens if the game goes like this?
How can I...
[Seongmin] It could be decided right away
[English] Will I be able to fight any more?
I don't know
[Jongkook] My thoughts too
[Referee speaks in Korean] Wait a minute
[Chaehyun] Let’s see, it’s not that deep.
- [Yoonchan] Is it deep?
- It's not deep, it's not deep.
- You didn't put any bond on it.
- [Yoon Chan] I didn’t add it.
But is it okay, though?
[Referee] Yes, yes, you can
That kind of injury right now
Boxers wake up very often
Then stop the bleeding
The bleeding stops.
If it spreads further, I will stop.
[English] Can you fight?
[Elasticity of the end]
[Jongkook in Korean]
Oh, can I see you one more time? Okay
Okay, this last time
I'll just watch it one round at a time, the last one.
uh
This was the shortest one, I did 10 rounds.
[♪ Heavy music]
[Yoonchan] It was a shame
Still, I have to do it till the end.
I have to do my best, for now
[Referee] Open your eyes, are you okay?
Is there any pain?
- There is a little bit.
- [Referee] A little bit, right? Yeah
[Shin Dong-hyun] ‘Big trouble happened’
'Huh, how does this work?'
Just one last round
I said I would do more
'Oh, this is really just
'I can't help it'
‘I really have to KO him no matter what.’
[ding bell sound]
- [Referee] Box
- [Kim Min-woo] Confidently, confidently
[Park Young-ho] Wow, it’s the last time, fighting
Burn it down, nice!
[Dex] Uh, Shin Dong-hyun, huh...
[Park Young-ho] Let’s pour it out
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Referee] Stop!
I should have done that a long time ago
[Participants] Hey
[Hyunjun] Oh, good
More, more, more, it's the last time
[Minwoo Kim] Breathe deeply
[Chaehyun] To be honest, I was worried.
[Park Young-ho] I have too much stamina left.
Wow! Hey, sleep
[Participants’ exclamation]
Aiming for KO, now
[Referee] Box!
[Participants] Hey, hey
Oh, hey, hey, hey
I'll send it, I'll send it
[Shin Dong-hyun] Now is the time to meet Lim Yun-chan
It's an opportunity to let go
I thought
[Taekmin] So you were saving your strength?
[Currently] Once you send it, it’s over.
[Minwoo Kim] Yes
I think I can finish it
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Dongseok] Oh, I got caught.
[Chaehyun] Ah, Yunchan has lost his strength.
I got hurt too
I'm worried about your wounds.
[Shin Dong-hyun] Well, Lim Yun-chan
I think I had the upper hand
'After 10 rounds,
I'll really send it to you'
Just timing like this
I think I was watching
[Participant] Hey
[Referee] Stop!
[Full time] Wow, this is...
[Participant] 10 seconds!
[Referee] Box!
Break, stop!
[Tingling bell sound]
Now, last, last
[Park Young-ho] Oh, I poured it all out?
[Hyunjun] Now, last fight!
- Fighting, it's the last time, the last time
- [Minwoo Kim] Show me, Donghyun.
[Current] Lee Chae-hyun fighting
[Kim Min-woo] Shin Dong-hyun fighting!
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Box!
[Full-time] You have to pour it out, you have to pour it out
- [Participant] Hey
- [Kim Min-woo] Okay, two hits.
[Hyunjun] I have to go, I have to go
Try it with pressure, it's short.
[Park Young-ho] Good, good
[Shin Dong-hyun] Lee Chae-hyun
Didn’t you feel a bit weak?
[♪ Suspenseful music]
‘We have to fight against each other to win, in the second half’
I was a bit confused
Because they push in
‘Do not add as much as possible.
'Don't give distance with your front hand'
[Shin Dong-hyun] ‘Ah, just now
'I need to put more pressure on it.'
‘I have to KO’
[Dex] Low aggression
Ugh, uhhu
[B-ball in English] Cheong Corner is strong.
[Dex in Korean] Last 20 seconds!
- [Kim Min-woo] It’s the last 20 seconds.
- [Dex] Last!
- [Hyunjun] I have to go in.
- [Dex] 15 seconds!
- [Kim Min-woo] It’s the last 15 seconds.
- [Park Young-ho] Show me!
[Yoonchan]
‘The game could change a bit’
I think he was worried
- Fighting Chaehyun Lee
- [Park Young-ho] We’re all here
- [Junseo] Donghyun, 15 seconds
- [Park Young-ho] Okay, we’re here.
- [Junseo] Donghyun, 15 seconds, 10 seconds
- [Park Young-ho] 10 seconds, 10 seconds
[Dex] 10, 9!
[Park Young-ho] Let’s go, let’s go to the engine
Ehey!
[Dex] 5 seconds!
[Kim Min-woo] Just do one more thing
Just do one more thing
[Dongseok] You have to hit it!
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop!
[Park Young-ho] Kabbi, ah!
It was good, it was good
[Chaehyun] In the second half
Actually, it was the most urgent.
There are some things that didn't go as planned.
So I was very worried.
[Jongkook] Ambiguous, ambiguous, this
[Dex] What should I do? This
[♪ Music filled with tension]
[English] Hong corner is the last
I couldn't show it in the second round.
Back corner Lee Chae-hyun
Looks more like a boxer
[Songseok’s response]
have good skills
I am Cheong Corner Shin Dong-hyun too
I think you did well
[Dongseok] The two of you did equally well.
[Park Young-ho in Korean]
Do you think Donghyun will rise?
[Hyunjun] I think the back corner will rise
Chaehyun?
No, ah, I don't know.
I really don't know this
[Assembly] Result of referee decision
The survivor of this fight is
[Participant] Indeed
[Chaehyun] ‘Wouldn’t I go up?
Still, I was clean.'
[Shin Dong-hyun] ‘Please call me Cheong’
Please say Cheong’
None
[Hyunjun] Wow
[♪ Heavy music]
Huh?
[Hyunjun] Are we all eliminated?
[Park Young-ho] Oh my
[Chaehyun] I was shocked.
'Am I really going home like this?'
[Shin Dong-hyun] What is missing?
'Then what, we
What, are they all eliminated?'
[Dongseok] This showdown
After consulting with a B-ball player,
We'll go into overtime
After discussion, we will proceed with overtime.
[♪ Music full of tension]
Overtime
We will only play with two players
With Lee Chae-hyeon
This is Shin Dong-hyun.
Okay
[Dongseok] This is Shin Dong-hyun.
[Yoon Chan] I gave in cleanly.
There was also butting.
Even when I felt
I can't play anymore
I thought about it
From then on, I supported Chaehyun hyung.
[Chaehyun] Now that it’s like this
I have to fight for Yunchan’s share as well.
overtime
We will proceed in 5 minutes.
- [Park Young-ho] Wow
- [Full-time] 5 minutes
5 minutes?
Wow, 5 minutes
[Shin Dong-hyun] Ah, okay, 5 minutes is good.
[Minwoo Kim] Brother
I remember running around
[Shin Dong-hyun] It’s advantageous
I thought about it
[Dongseok in English]
Let's see what happens
Box!
[ding bell sound]
[♪ Somber music]
[Participants] Fighting!
[Kim Min-woo in Korean] Shin Dong-hyun, let’s go
[Participant] Good
[Minwoo Kim] Donghyun hyung, show me
[Park Young-ho] It’s your showtime
[Shin Dong-hyun] In the beginning
I kept pressing.
[Participants’ exclamation]
Lee Chae-hyeon is now taking a shot at me.
Aren't you a little scared?
'I really try not to get hit.
'You're paying a lot of attention'
[Participant 1’s elasticity]
[Participant 2] Good body
[Participant 3] One shot, one shot, impact
[English] Cheong Corner is powerful
[Songseok’s response]
It also has aggression.
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Chaehyun in Korean]
How strong is your punching power?
You have good strength
It was a bit frustrating because there was no defense.
[Standard] Wow, that's too much right?
[Yoonchan] A little
I think he was worried
[Yoonchan] Hyung, it’s okay
Bro, it's okay, bro, it's okay
[Current] Wow
Did it take a lot of force?
[Seongmin] You have to take it lightly
[Chaehyun] ‘Relax as calmly as possible.
'Let's go at my own pace'
- [Seongmin] Boy, did you dodge well.
- [Standard] Child
[Park Young-ho] That friend is definitely avoiding me.
Just because the performance is good
[Taekmin] I’m running it well
[Park Young-ho] It runs well.
[♪ Intense music]
[Seongmin] Good distance control
Ah, Lee Chae-hyeon
I really like the distance
It doesn't fit well
[Chaehyun] The streets
You didn't catch it well.
[Seongmin] Ah, I avoided it well.
[Chaehyun] Because I have to go up
I was thinking about the operation
Hit the opponent with a front hand jab
To go with the feeling of being gnawed
[Yunchan] Wow, good, good jab
[Hyunjae] All jabs are correct
[Chaehyun] ‘Relax a lot.
'I have to catch it and eat it'
[♪ Heavy music]
nice jab
[Present] Oh, it’s good
[Dongseok] I keep losing stamina
If you get hit like that
[Shin Dong-hyun] That’s it
It was a very annoying punch.
Do you feel like someone keeps touching you?
something keeps on scoring
I felt like I was being taken away.
So, ‘Oh, I guess I’ll have to push myself a bit, again.’
[Participant and Dex] Hey
- [Referee] Break, stop, stop
- [Dex] Oh, butting again, butting?
Butting, now...
[♪ dark music]
It wasn't torn, right?
[Referee] Stop
[Chaehyun] IC
[Yunchan] Is it torn?
Is it torn?
- [Present] No bleeding? Doesn't it sound?
- [Participant] Yes
[Chaehyun] The doctor
I'm afraid they'll just stop it, so I say 'no'
Then I lose.
- [Referee] That’s it.
- [Chaehyun] Continue...
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
[Referee] If there is blood
You can stop
It can't be helped
- Box!
- [Park Young-ho] Fighting
[Dex and participant] 1 minute and 30 seconds!
[Hyunjun] I have to go, I have to go
1 minute 30 seconds now, I have to go
Okay, brother
1 minute, 1 minute and 20 seconds left, 1 minute and 20 seconds left
[Yoonchan] When I looked, I saw blood.
My worries became reality
[Yunchan] Hyung, are you okay?
[Hyunjae] I have to stretch out, I have to stretch out
I have to go fist
[Hyunjun] If you wait, it’s too late
- [Participants] 10 seconds
- [Referee] Stop, stop
- [Taekmin] Oh, I’m bleeding
- [Chaehyun] Oh, it’s okay.
- [Referee] No, no
- Oh, I'll just go.
[Dongseok] Is there cutting?
[Minwoo Kim] Wow, you got cut.
It's okay, it's okay
- [Dongseok] Looks like there is a cut.
- It's okay, it's okay.
[Dex] Ah...
[Referee] Cut, cut
[Jongkook] Oh, there’s blood.
[Chaehyun] I’m afraid it will become a doctor stop
I'll stick it, I'll stick it
[Chaehyun] I’m worried
It was too much, honestly.
I can play
‘I don’t care if it bleeds or tears’
‘Please don’t stop the game’
[rustling sound]
[♪ Somber music]
Should I proceed?
Is it possible to proceed?
- It didn't break much.
- [Doctor] Yes
[Chaehyun] Ah, I really want to cling to you.
[Referee] Now, if you bleed,
Not right away
[Chaehyun] Yes
[Minwoo Kim] I can do it, I can do it
[Yoonchan] Lee Chaehyun, fighting!
[Chaehyun] To the Muay Thai athlete
I thought I couldn't lose
I was so desperate, really.
- [Seokseok and Referee] Box!
- [Park Young-ho] Come on, fighting
Now, last, fighting!
[Participants] Fighting
[Participant 1] Hey
[Participant 2’s elasticity]
[Participant 3] That’s right
[Chaehyun] Just use my remaining strength
Let's pour it all out and come down
[English] That player is really crazy
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Taekmin in Korean] Ah, now Donghyun
Maybe it's because that person just poured it all out.
Do you feel a little tired now?
[♪ Exciting music]
[Participant 1] Big, big
[Participant 2]
The movement is big, the movement is big
[Shin Dong-hyun] Because I’m aiming for just one shot too much
That one shot didn’t work well.
[English] Back corner
He's a better boxer.
yes, that's right
- [Korean] Chaehyun Lee, fighting
- [Participant 1] We’re all here
- [Participant 2] 10 seconds, 10 seconds
- Lee Chae-hyun, just do it for 10 seconds.
[Participants] 10 seconds!
[Park Young-ho] I came, I came, I came, right away
It’s one room
[Kim Min-woo] Okay
[Tingling bell sound]
- [Referee] Stop!
- [Participants] Hey
[Dongseok] Well done, good job
[Shin Dong-hyun] Strong punches
Because I hit a lot
‘It’s worth a try’
[Chaehyun] Unconditionally
I thought I won
[Dex] What kind of player is this?
Are you a better player?
With a player who has one strong shot...
Technically, I guess
A friend who is complete is better
Something a little punchy
To some extent, I am also born with it.
[Dex] Ah
The survivor of this fight is
[♪ Nervous music]
[Park Young-ho] Writes
Do you think Donghyun will rise?
But the style that B-ball likes is
Isn't it over there?
[Dongseok] The survivor of this battle is
This is Lee Chae-hyun from the back corner.
[Participants applause]
[Chaehyun] Ah!
[♪ Intense music]
[Taekmin] Soldier guy, cool guy
[Chaehyun] It was really hard
Still won
It's really good
Oh really
So much that I can't express it in words
good
That's because I worked really hard
That I was in the top 5
I have to prove it
with my skills
[Jongkook] Now, our Hong corner
Lim Yun-chan
Feelings after the battle
How do you feel?
I was trying to quit boxing...
Because of the real ‘I Am Boxer’
I want to box again
I think I heard it
In fact, while boxing
Because I had very few good memories.
[♪ Calm music]
With my father
I fight a lot because of this boxing.
[Yunchan’s yummy mouth sound]
Well, after competing professionally
While my father was suffering from illness
He passed away
Dad is sick
I came out to do boxing.
My father looked at me like that
You said ‘I’m really proud’
[Crying] In the end
After my father passed away
Just drink and drink
I hardly ever box anymore.
Actually, I don't want to exercise.
But what, Chaehyun hyung?
Now again at the beginning of this year
Because we met
While exercising together
Boxing is also so much fun
[♪ Hopeful music]
But still
I think boxing is so much fun
What the future looks like
I think it's more important
my attitude toward life
I think it was an opportunity to change something.
Thank you so much, thank you
[Bvol in English] First of all, very good
I would say it was a game.
your story
It was nice to hear it
I also love boxing a lot
Boxing has helped my life a lot
Boxing kept me centered.
through boxing
I found another family
Even though we fight in the ring
we are
Because it's just one boxing game.
I want to see you again somewhere later
Do you do boxing?
hope you continue
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Narration in Korean] Sampajeon
The next participant is
box
- [Participants] Fighting
- [Referee] Box
[Participants’ exclamation]
[♪ Intense music]
Hey
- [Participant 1] Good
- [Participant 2] Hey
[Dex] Kwon Oh-gon
What today, very
You look to be in good condition?
[Dongseok] Ogon has relaxed, now
[Seongmin] Oh!
[Participants] Hey
[English] You're really good at the back corner.
[Dex in Korean] Kwon Oh-gon
I feel like my fists are really fast, wow
[Dongseok] The survivor of this battle is
This is Kwon Oh-gon.
[Participants’ exclamation and applause]
[♪ Intense music]
[Narration] The next participant is
box
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Box
[Seongmin] Fighting!
[♪ Interesting music]
- [Chaehyun] That’s right
- [Seongmin] Oh wow
Oh, I'm good at avoiding it.
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Dex] Oh, Lee Ki-jun, uh
[English] I like Lee Ki-jun
[Taekmin in Korean]
Giwon has good technique.
Seungjun has good physical strength.
How do these two
It depends...
[Jongkook] Oh wow
I like my feet, I really like my feet
[Participants’ exclamation]
But Lee Ki-jun is so good.
[Jongkook’s response]
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Tingling bell sound]
The survivor of this fight is
This is Lee Ki-jun, Cheong Corner.
[Participants’ exclamation and applause]
[Junseo] Unimaginable
It was a place.
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Hyunjun] It’s finally come.
[Shin Dong-hyun] Again
I have a chance
‘Let’s make sure to achieve it’
[Songseok] Box!
[ding bell sound]
- [Participant 1] Hey
- [Participant 2] Hey, hey
[Participant 3] Now, now
[Participant 4] No, raise it!
Don't try to avoid it, raise it, raise it
[Participant 5] Come on
Last, go for it, yeah
[Junseo] From here
I will fight fiercely
[Seungjun] I will win no matter what
[Hyunjun] I will definitely win
[Park Young-ho] There’s a big game left.
[♪ Somber music]
[Chaehyun] Uh, what is it? Who's left?
[Current] Kim Dong-hoe, Kim Taek-min, Hong Seong-min
[Seungjun] Wow, the last group
It's really awesome, isn't it?
[Park Young-ho] This is a really great three-way match.
[Dex] Ah, but really
'Once like this
'I want to put it on'
I had an idea
- I never thought I would actually see this.
- Yeah, that's right.
[Hyundai] But this
The last one will be fun, just
Ha, the three strongest players are competing.
[Narration] Back Corner Hong Seong-min
[♪ Rhythmic music]
[Participant] Wow
[Participants applause]
- [Minwoo Kim] Fighting
- [Seungjun] Main game
[Current] Tyson Hong Fighting
[Park Young-ho] Back corner with good win rate
[Narration] Hong Connor, Kim Dong-hoe
[Dongseok] It’s
[English] That player
Won for 14 consecutive years
14 years? At a national competition?
Oh, that's interesting.
[Narration in Korean] Cheong Corner
Kim Taek-min
[Park Young-ho] Come on
[Participants’ exclamation]
- Hey, come on
- [Minwoo Kim] Big game, big game
[Jongkook] Ah, the member
It must be very difficult, right?
Hey, how
Did you think about adding three people like this?
[B-ball in English] They are heavyweights.
[Songseok’s response]
Sounds fun.
[Chaehyun in Korean]
Hey, this is really amateur.
An amateur triad like this...
[Seongmin] ‘You’re finally doing it’
[♪ Somber music]
Now when it airs here
‘Someday, Taekmin hyung and I will
I thought, ‘I’ll give it a try.’
The time has come
[Taekmin] Me and Donghoe hyung
almost four times a week
Full sparring?
we know each other so well
Hong Seong-min’s play
Because I know too well
It's a match against top Korean players.
I am confident that I will win it all
Ah, the business team, now as the eldest brother
As an old man
I want to show that I am ‘alive’
[Park Young-ho] No matter who wins this
It doesn't seem strange, does it?
Well, it's going to be crazy today.
Fighting, fighting
[Participants] Fighting, fighting
[Park Young-ho] Hey, the pressure is different.
[Minwoo Kim] Oh, really
All the weight...
Only one of them is going up.
That doesn't make sense.
[Donghoe] I’ll show you
[Seongmin] I know it’s not easy
I'll definitely show it to you
Box!
[ding bell sound]
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Referee] Box
- [Participants] Fighting, fighting
[♪ Music full of tension]
[Donghoe] With Seongmin
Because it's my first time
Physical fitness management
Now I've done some light exploring.
[Participants] Hey
[Taekmin] Make it louder, cover
[Seongmin] Me too
I tried to read it to some extent
It was a round to warm up.
[Participants’ exclamation]
[Dongseok] Hey
[Elasticity of the end]
[Jongkook in English]
It's a different level, right?
[Korean] Ah, but Kim Dong-hoe
It weighs 10kg more
[Current] Seongmin, cover closely
You have to hit it while stepping in.
Seongmin, as you step in
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop!
- [Dex] First thing, lightly, yeah
- [Dongseok] Yes, I saw it.
- [Dex] Just seeing the tide
- I saw the liver.
[Chaehyun] It’s okay
[Seongmin] I’m a bit low in weight class
As I was doing it
If you go back, you will be physically
I thought I might be pushed away
I was afraid
[♪ Heavy music]
[Seungjun and Sanggeun’s elasticity]
This is breathtaking, this is
[Taekmin] To be honest,
I was confident
30 rounds, 40 rounds
After 50 rounds
In the end I win
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Now
Box!
[♪ Music full of tension]
Kim Dong-hoe plays very softly, doesn’t he?
[Participant 1] Wow
Wow
[Participant 2] Wow, what is it?
[Participant 3] Wow, wow
[Chaehyun] Donghae player
You're really wandering around.
[Donghoe] The operation is now
Because I don’t have enough stamina
Avoid and evade the opponent's attacks
Increase the tempo little by little
I thought I should upload it
[Referee] Now, it’s survival.
[ding ding bell]
Stop! uh
[Taekmin] In the first round, it was like this
I think it was done defensively.
Because
You have to do 30 or 40 rounds.
‘Just play good defense.
'Let's not be greedy'
It's going to catch fire here.
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Now, box!
[Dongseok] You two have style
They are similar
[Dex] Yeah, it’s really a bit similar.
Just like this
[Dongseok] Hey
[Participants] Hey
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Seongmin] Be confident
I think I tried to punch him.
[Hyunjun] Hey
Hey, good stabbing.
I'm stabbing well
Hey
That's right
Shake it, shake it
Hong Seong-min is aiming for a counter right now.
[People's surprised exclamations]
[Tingling bell sound]
- Oh, my god.
- [Dex] Hey
[English] That was a good uppercut
[ding bell sound]
[Referee speaks in Korean] Now, box!
Uh, okay, I like you to sit down.
[Chaehyun] Yes
Rhythm, rhythm, Seongminah
[Hyunjun] That’s right, shake it, shake it
[Donghoe] Just swinging doesn’t hit
[♪ Suspenseful music]
Impact one by one
[Hyunjun] Oh, the movement is good.
Hey
Seongmin, it’s good.
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop, uh
[Seongmin] Huh...
[Hyunjae] Good, the pace is good now
[Park Young-ho] Donghoe must be the most difficult, right?
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Now, box!
Box!
[♪ Nervous music]
That's right, Kim Taek-min
I have to go in now
[Dongseok] Breaking the rhythm like that
If you don't fight, you can't win
[B-ball in English] Kim Dong-hoe
You're doing it like you're training.
not a game
Looks like they're training
[Jongkook’s response]
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop!
[Korean] Ah, Kim Dong-hoe
I don't know what's going on, well...
Just spit, take it easy, yeah
[Dongseok] Kim Dong-hoe too
You can't let down your guard
If you do it like that
Because we could end it
[Jongkook] Yes, yes
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Now
- [Participant] Fighting
- [Referee] Box!
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Current] Seong Min-ah
You also need to raise your gear a little bit.
- [Dex] You’re doing great!
- [Participants] Hey
That's right!
- [Dex] That’s right!
[Participant] Hey
Hey
Oh, I aimed for one.
[Hyunjun] Hey, I enjoyed it, hey!
[Participants’ exclamation]
[♪ Interesting music]
[Jongkook] Ah, but the rhythm is good
Hong Seongmin today
[Dongseok] Taekmin has a fist
I'm not getting along well with Hong Seong-min.
[Tingling bell sound]
[Referee] Stop!
Like vipers, like vipers
[Seongmin] ‘Ah, this is the beginning’
I had this feeling
Not losing momentum
I think I thought it was important
[Donghoe] I still don’t have the stamina.
‘Let’s go slowly and carefully’
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Now, box!
[Chaehyun] Seongminah
Good rhythm, get the rhythm
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Hyunjae] Oh, Seongmin is nice
I have good quickness and, uh, I'm doing well.
[ding bell sound]
Be confident!
[Dongseok] Go in, go in
Wouldn’t it slowly shift gears?
If you don't go hard, it's your own loss.
- Yes
- [Jongkook] Ah...
[Donghoe] ‘Now it’s metallurgy
'I have to attack'
[Taekmin] Round
Because I said it was infinite
It's just the beginning
[Seongmin] Now I don’t have any stamina or anything.
I have to keep pushing forward.
Fighting, fighting!
[English] Let’s watch 3 more rounds
[♪ Heavy music]
[Jongkook] Just 3 rounds?
[Korean] One last lap!
One last lap!
[Donghoe] ‘Now?’
'This is the last time?'
[Taekmin] Is this what happens?
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Now, box!
[Seongmin] It’s an operation and I don’t have any thoughts about that.
Strength at the end
I tried to pour it all out
[♪ Music full of tension]
[Dongseok] I like the rhythm, uh
[Jongkook] I like shaking my head
Oh, I like the cover, nice.
[Participant 1] Hey, hey
[Participant 2] Good movement
[Dongseok] Kim Dong-hoe is usually
some other players
I won easily and easily
Today will be very difficult
[Jongkook] So,
[Donghoe] Now I can even tie the ring.
I use it a lot but
I corner it and attack it.
Since there is no ring line
attack flow
It had a tendency to keep breaking up.
[Participant 1’s elasticity]
[Participant 2] Hey
Hey
One went, one went
Fish oil!
[Songseok] Oh!
Hey
[Dex] It’s bloody
[Taekmin] Huh
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop!
[MC’s elasticity]
Is today good?
[Elasticity of Dex]
[Dongseok in English] You like the back corner, right?
[B-Bol’s response]
Hong Seong-min is better than other players
showed a good performance
[Present is in Korean]
Oh, Seongmin is nice.
Seongmin, take a deep breath.
I'm doing well
[♪ Heavy music]
[Taekmin] Donghoe hyung is a bit
I saw you having a hard time
I, in my eyes
[Dongseok] Now, Donghoe Kim
Because of physical strength
[Jongkook] Right?
It seems like it's coming a little bit, right? stamina
Definitely at a disadvantage compared to these two players
[ding bell sound]
[Referee] Now, box!
I'm one of three, bro.
One out of three, fighting
Have an image, emphasize it!
[Jongkook] Too passive, ah...
Now, everyone, work harder!
[♪ Intense music]
[Referee] Come inside the circle
[Dex] Push it in!
[ding ding bell]
[Referee] Stop!
I don't know who's ahead
[♪ dark music]
[Dongseok] I’m tired
[상근] 진짜 힘들 것 같다
[Donghoe] There’s nothing to show.
It's over?
Ha...
[Donghoe] It was a bit frustrating.
[Present] Fighting, fighting!
[Taekmin] Donghoe looks like he’s tired too.
‘I will win’
[Seongmin] ‘Even if I fall,
‘I’ll have to pour everything into this round.’
- [Park Young-ho] Fighting
- [Referee] Now
- [Hyunjun] Round 8, rhythm!
- [Referee] Box!
[♪ Intense music]
[Hyunjun] I think it’s the last time, good!
[Donghoe] Hey
Don’t take it out, Seongmin.
That’s right!
Now fucking
Now I have to hit it, now
- [Participant 1] That’s right.
- [Participant 2] Hey
last round
That's it, 50 seconds!
[Hyunjun] This is the last, this is the last
[Dex] It’s the last time, the last time
No more!
[Elasticity]
[Chaehyun] Seongmin, focus.
I like the rhythm, I like the rhythm
[Dex] No need to save strength!
There is no turning back, now!
[Participants] Hey, hey
Wow, what is it?
[Participant] Okay, okay, okay
Hey!
[Park Young-ho]
I think they're both crazy, but
[Participants] Hey!
[Dex] Fighting!
[Participants’ exclamation]
- [Hyunjun] 10 seconds, last 10 seconds!
- [Dex] 10 seconds!
- Hey
- [Participant] I got on board
- [Referee] Now, come into the circle.
- [Participants] Hey, hey!
[Referee] Come inside the circle
- Come inside the circle!
- [Hyunjae] Seongmin, don’t get excited.
[Referee] Stop!
It's so crazy, wow
[Dongseok in English] How did you see it?
I don't know, I
[Jongkook’s laughter]
[Dongseok] You have to pick one person, no matter what.
[B-ball] I don’t know this time
[Korean] Oh, they don’t know
[B-ball in English] This player is
There was no impact
[Dongseok] I seemed tired
[Korean] Who won?
[♪ Nervous music]
Referee decision result
The survivor of this fight is
[Donghoe] This is
It's a game you never know no matter who gives it to you.
[Seongmin] Still
I showed you what I had to show you
[Taekmin] To be honest,
I'm getting greedy
[Dongseok] The survivor of this battle is
Back corner, this is Hong Seong-min.
[Participants’ surprised exclamation and applause]
[Full-time] Well done, well done, everything
[Dongseok] All three
You fought well.
Today, Hong Seong-min’s rhythm
Everything was kind of nice.
Especially today
[♪ Rhythmic music]
I did a good job
[Seongmin] I feel good and happy
I am not intimidated
what i can do
I moved more passionately
Couldn’t I have won?
‘I really need to prepare harder’
I think about it
I think the game was disappointing
I just feel regretful
Seongmin did a good job
Respect
[Dongseok] Survived the three-way battle
Congratulations to the five players
[Participants applause]
[Participant] A
[♪ Rhythmic music]
[English] Congratulations, everyone.
I wish you luck in your future
through this experience
I wish I learned more
incredibly
Because it was a valuable experience
Congratulations again
good luck
[Jongkook in Korean] Good
[Chaehyun] Because I’m in the top 5 now
I have to win
[Standard] Do your best
I will win
[Ogon] The remaining games are
I will do my best to overwhelm you.
[Seongmin] Because I’m in the top 5
I'm getting a little greedy now.
[Currently] Fast crab
How scary is it?
let me show you
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Junseo] Unimaginable
It was a place.
[Hyeonjun] ‘This scene
'I can see it'
‘It’s finally come.’
[Dongseok] I have to do this until I die
[Junseo] Crazy, crazy
- [Dongseok] I can see Namsan over there too.
- [Dex] So,
Where can I find a visual like this?
[Jongkook] Yes, usually when we were young
- They say, ‘Follow me to the rooftop.’
- [Dex] That’s right.
- 'Follow me, follow me to the prison land'
- [Dex] ‘Follow me to prison’
'Are you that good at teasing?'
[Jongkook’s laughter]
‘Follow me to prison’
[Jongkook in English]
What do you think of this stage?
It's really beautiful, it's beautiful
[Jongkook’s laughter]
The highest place in Seoul
I think it came
[Jongkook] At the top of the building
Have you ever played a game?
I've never, never tried it
[Dex's laughter]
[Korean] That’s right
[Dongseok] Okay, so this place is
This is our death match location.
We have now discussed
Among the ten, among the ten eliminated
Just select six people
[♪ Meaningful music]
I played three matches today
I decided to pass additional exams
[Jongkook’s response]
- [Dongseok] This friend is also such a waste.
- [Jongkook] Oh, who is it?
[♪ Meaningful music]
[Dex] Well, Yuk Jun-seo too
I once...
[Dongseok] Uh, me too, me too
[Dex] That's aggressive
It feels so good
[English] I think
I think this person did a good job
[Dongseok in Korean] Hey, this is me
I wish I could pick one
I wish I could do it one more time
This friend
- [Dex] Seungjun Kook
- [Jongkook] I like it
[English] This is an MMA fighter, right?
[Jongkook’s response]
[Korean] I miss Hyunjun too
[Seat] Okay
- [Dex] It's coming again, it's coming again
- [Jongkook] It's coming, it's coming
[♪ Somber music]
Hey
[Elasticity of Dex]
[Jongkook] Oh, it’s cool, really.
[Dex] Looks like ‘Gladiator’
'Gladiator'
[Participant 1] Wow!
[Park Young-ho] Wow, this is
What's going on again?
[Participant 2’s lament]
[Shin Dong-hyun] Ah, again this night
I guess I'll do something on the rooftop.
[Junseo] Since we’ve come this far
I will fight fiercely here.
[Park Young-ho] It’s not over yet
[Jongkook] Wow, that won’t be easy, right?
Now, b-ball player.
death match
Please make it public
[English] This death match is
It's a tire brawl.
[♪ Meaningful music]
[MC’s elasticity]
[Participant's elasticity]
[Seungjun in Korean] Tire fight
[Park Young-ho] Ha, Lord
[Hyunjun] What are those tires?
[Seungjun] That narrow place
This is where I fight.
[Junseo] Well, I’ve never tried it before.
Wow, how does that work?
[Jongkook] Now, this death match
How the tire brawl progresses
Let me explain.
What about the two players?
Let's each put one foot in the tire.
Uh, let's have a boxing match.
tire brawl
It is carried out as a single
[English] I think we need to stop
stop, stop
[Tingling bell sound]
[Jongkook in Korean] Master
Until the end is declared
The showdown continues
Now, in this death match
Who will survive?
Out of a total of six
There are three people
- [Shin Dong-hyun] Oh
- [Park Young-ho] Wow, three people?
[♪ Heavy music]
Half of it comes alive
[Minwoo Kim] Here
Three more people come out alive
It was really boiling over.
[Junseo] I have to defeat my opponent
That's living
[Jongkook] If there is a KO match
Survival or elimination is decided immediately.
[Shin Dong-hyun] I have to KO him
When there is no KO winner
By the master's decision
Decide the final survivor
[Park Young-ho] I have to shake it all off until the end.
[Kim Min-woo] Loser Resurrection Battle
Let’s really pour it out since it’s the last time
[Seungjun] Looking higher
It's going up
[Dex] Ah, I
I don't think I can do it because I'm scared, honestly.
From this close distance...
[♪ Intense music]
[Jongkook] Death match, tire brawl
We will announce the contestants
[Dongseok] Who will participate in the death match?
This is Park Young-ho.
[Jongkook] But I have good physical strength
Because I have strength and weight
[Seungjun] Ha, I’m scared, I’m scared
[Minwoo Kim] ‘I want to avoid it’
What about Park Young-ho?
'The weight you can bear
I thought, ‘I have it.’
[♪ Suspenseful music]
Because strength is no joke.
[Shin Dong-hyun’s laughter]
[Shin Dong-hyun] Oh, it’s really scary.
I practiced really hard
short upper
Here we have to do it like an engine.
[Park Young-ho] Anyway, I
Fighting, something like this
There's a lot of brawling now.
Because it's my style
‘Oh, it would be advantageous for me’
[Dongseok] The player we will compete against is
This is Kook Seungjun.
[People applauding]
[Minwoo Kim] This is real
I think Seungjun will be at a disadvantage.
[B-ball in English]
The difference between the two is 21 kg.
[Songseok] 21kg? That's awesome
[Korean] There is a bit of a difference in weight class.
[B-Ball in English] Seungjun Kook
He's a skillful player.
good skill player
[Songseok’s response]
And the skills are not good
big player
And a strong player
[Jongkook in Korean]
But the body has good durability.
You saw it earlier,
Because I endure it all
[Park Young-ho] I was confident
Honestly, I was confident, really.
[♪ Rhythmic music]
You mixed it with Seungjun Kook.
A little out fighting
He said he was going to do it now.
But if you tie it like this
Because I’m infighting
'Huh, I guess it's worth a try?'
I think I had some thoughts.
Ugh, I was so worried.
'If I really get hit, I'll die.'
Still have boxing experience
It hasn't been that long
made with technology
Body combination or
Use something like this
Just what I am
I have to show you everything.
[♪ Suspenseful music]
[Dongseok] Death match, tire brawl
Let the fight begin
box
[ding bell sound]
- [Referee] Now, box.
- [Junseo] Fighting
[Jongkook] Oh, okay
[Shin Dong-hyun] While breathing
[♪ Nervous music]
fish oil
Yeah, okay, just go with it.
[Hyunjun] That’s right
Hook body, hook body
- Ah, targeting Bodhi, wow.
- [Dongseok] I'm hitting the body, that's it.
[Seungjun] Because you’re only raising your guard
Keep looking for a gap
Attacks like the stomach, hooks, etc.
I tried to do a lot
[Hyunjun] Hey, okay
[Jongkook] Uh, I like it, uh, I like the short.
[♪ Exciting music]
[Shin Dong-hyun] Shortly, briefly, briefly
briefly, briefly
[Park Young-ho] Actually, that
Just like in the previous game
He hit Bodhi a lot.
But I have a good body
I have never fallen before
[Dongseok] Seungjun
Guard up, guard up
[Park Young-ho]
Did you feel like you were hit?
[Shin Dong-hyun] Hey!
hey!
[♪ Intense music]
- Hey, hey, hey!
- [Hyunjun] Lower your posture, stand taller
[Shin Dong-hyun] Briefly, briefly
- Guard once, then do maintenance.
- [Jongkook] Guard, guard
- Oh, Park Young-ho is a tough guy.
- [Dongseok] Oh, okay.
Oh!
[Shin Dong-hyun] I’ll lose my strength after a while
Well, if you hold on just a little longer, you'll lose strength.
Hey, breathing, Youngho, yeah, uh
- [Hyunjun] There is a difference in strength
- [Participant] Hey
- [Hyunjun] No, raise it!
- [Shin Dong-hyun] Hey, hey
[Hyunjun] Don’t try to avoid me
Look up, look up, look up
[Participants’ exclamation]
[♪ Nervous music]
Players who will participate in the death match
[Dex] Two people who are the pride of Muay Thai
[Kim Min-woo] Like a crazy dog
I will bite everything
box
[Dex] I went in, I went in
- [Dongseok] Uh, down.
- [Referee] Down!
[Shin Dong-hyun] Hey, hey, hey, continue
Don't stop, don't stop
[English] Continue, continue, continue
Keep going, keep going!
[Korean] Three seats are empty.
Oh, you didn't come out?
Aren't you hiding?
[♪ Rhythmic music]
[Man] Dear viewers,
Hello!
'I Am Boxer' quarterfinal match
I'll greet you
With commentator Kyu-won Lee
I'll tell you
This is caster Seong Seung-heon.
[Chaehyun] I will definitely win
[Currently] I don’t know who I’ll end up with
Be nervous
[Audience cheers]
[Seungheon] Now, player Yang
Let's meet for round 1
Box!
[ding bell sound]
[♪ Rhythmic music]
[♪ Theme song]